these flying piglens have been making me
a very rich hermit check it out i've got
many
many stacks of gold blocks and etho has
very swiftly i must say produced not
only the storage system
but also the piglin station over here
they are ready to trade i am ready to
give them gold and we are ready to get
all of these goodies and we are
particularly interested in things like
obsidian crying obsidian and black stone
so it might not be the prettiest thing
and i'm hoping v dubs is going to come
here and make this a little more pretty
yeah even ether said make look good so
let's submit all of this gold
and see what we can get out of it that
is that is a lot of gold
okay let's see let's check it out see
they all get dispensed a nice
gold bar they get they look at it for a
minute and then they decide what they're
going to trade with us lots of hermits
already have this farm so
i'm pretty sure we're not going to
profit majorly from this
but there is a reason to get this done
you do get an awful lot of goodies
so i would call this a pretty big
success and this was truly
truly teamwork to make the upside down
mansion productive and producing
lots and lots of goodies
so i think we leave this producing and
we maybe even take some of this stuff
out with us because there's another
thing i've been working on very secretly
now in the shopping district there is
this fella
and he's eating leaves now i did say a
long time ago that i wasn't gonna get
involved or collect a bunch of leaves in
fact i never even signed up and there's
no way for me to sign up now however i
kind of lied i have been collecting some
leaves so what i think i'm gonna do
is target ren diggity dog and i'm going
to see if he wants to team up because i
think i've collected few leaves
nine or ten
these stupid roadblocks
so if i can get ren to team up with me i
have a feeling we can claim
the prize the giant pile
of gold diamonds and netherrite
50 50 split with ren and just to prove
it check this out this is what it looks
like to be single-handedly responsible
for climate change on the hermitcraft
server
the devastation
that occurred
over many
many hours
round the back of my base look at this
this is a disgrace
this is an absolute it just keeps going
hours and hours and hours all so that we
could take
the win but this only works if i can get
rent in on this plan
i'm sure he's gonna be willing to take
me up on it
but if he doesn't
i've got thousands of leaves that i do
not need
this is only a small proportion of the
devastation that i've caused and any
people that come across this are going
to be like what on earth happened here
this is what climate change looks like
everyone it's serious and it's not funny
ren is online right now so all i need to
do is find him
and lure him to the giant pile of oak
leaves this is a serious amount every
single one of these shulker boxes
is full to the brim with leaves
which i hope will secure
the leaf game or the hedge games can't
remember what it's called
the only issue is i don't actually know
where ren is he wasn't at his base
the only other place really would be the
shopping district so now i want to lead
him without saying a word
we want to lead him we want to oh no not
the whole pile don't fall in his lava
come on follow
follow the leaves ren follow the
breadcrumbs
okay now we take off slowly
is he following
tell me he's following come on red yes
he's going
follow follow the leaves
and then
land where is he
have i lost him
oh whoa
the heck
and then we follow we come on and
then we lead him all the way to the pile
check it out
we'll let him figure this out because he
hasn't he doesn't know that i've been no
one knows that i've been doing this that
is the face of a man who has just
figured it out
bro this is a little bit insane what
what are you doing
so i said i wasn't going to join the
hedge games but then i just
did i just spent hours and hours causing
climate change on hermitcraft
oh oh like oh bernie like the bernie
competition exactly but i never really
signed up so like i need an in and i was
wondering right if you wanted to go
halfsies maybe we could steal the win i
have no idea how many are done i don't
really know how the game works i just
know you need leaves and a lot of them
yeah you d i mean i've put in quite a
lot but this is way more than i put in
like way more i mean we could go halves
i mean i was hoping to get the prize for
myself i've actually been collecting
some leaves
i can go and ask i can go and ask some
other people okay wait wait hold on
hold on i think the competition is
pretty close well i mean people have
been collecting so teaming up does sound
like a plan actually if if you come this
way
oh
i might be able to uh he's in my own
trick
i've fallen into the base using my own
trick against me
so i've also been collecting leaves
because i've had my eyeballs on that
competition
um
i actually won like two jackpots out of
it when i deposited so i've also been
very sneakily piling up
um
as well
i've been sneakily piling off some
leaves too
yo
so dude yeah i mean i don't want to brag
but my power is a little bigger than
yours your pile is bigger than mine kind
of sad but with our piles combined this
has got to be a win right
i don't know how much other people have
been gathering leaves but mine took like
two days flat of leaf gathering and i'm
not doing any more so if you want to go
halves these i'm going to go and submit
my boxes all right all right i'm in
let's do it sweets i couldn't submit
them without
you uh wren you're actually gonna have
to shut i don't actually know what to do
i've just got right boxes
okay well it's pretty easy uh we'll use
my box okay and all we gotta do is put
in one shulker box at a time and
bernie's teeth will light up when all
the
lamps are lit the game's over that's
enough leaves collected and apparently
we get some jackpots and stuff out of
this piece so dude there's only two yeah
there's two lights there's only
two lights yeah
okay so literally just one at a time one
at a time there we go i heard a ding
it's gonna take a while to do this yeah
okay i'll tell you what you put the
shulker boxes in i'll just slowly feed
your inventory with new ones okay
[Music]
yeah that's one tooth lit up jackpot the
lie ugh
dude
dude we got a short changed and we got
jackpot gg gravel and gold
i get it gg gravel and gold very smart
scale
something's happening
yes
more goodies nice okay okay okay
we got jackpot the nether
right sweet oh
and we got jackpot speed miner oh my
goodness gracious me
my goodness that is a good one that's a
good one
wow that's actually a really good one do
you think we have enough to light up one
more teeth um we're done we are done wow
we lit up two lamps
yeah i don't know i only made a cup of
tea during all of that that took ages it
took absolutely ages
yeah well there we go so four teeth i
mean is that a g no more you got no more
boxes left in your chest nowhere no
empty chest
okay we are done so we've just got to
hope that that's enough i mean that is a
lot of leaves that was an outrageous
amount of leaves if we don't win this i
i don't know what i'm going to do man i
might hit but the wall or something yeah
i mean hours spent on this
yeah also um what are we doing with the
expression we could let's go harvey's on
the jackpot let's go
yeah there we go and i'll have the cake
sweet okay sweet all right done done
deal
i don't know when do we find out if we
win i have no idea but if we don't win g
i'm gonna be sad so i've come back to
the upside down because i actually need
the service of this building it's the
ghastbusters and scar hasn't done an
interior he's just left three signs
place orders today gas busters hq open
during construction mob proofing mob
damage repair now i need this bit the
mob proofing because
if you stand in the gold farm and let
the
zombie piglets fall
unfortunately there are some spawning
points that are a problem that are
making this less efficient so i'm going
to give scar a job there's no
information on this whatsoever there's
no book there's no cost i is it pay what
you want or is it
pay nothing i'm not sure i could be
paying my soul for this please spawn
proof the upper part of the nether
mansion to improve the gold farm rates
test gold farm and see where the piggies
are spawning so hopefully this gives
scar a little i have done quite a lot of
mob spawning already but there are just
these little bits like up here that need
doing i did a lot of button placing out
the back here this has helped a bunch
but this isn't good enough they still
spawn out the back here and it still
needs improving
now speaking of errands there are a few
more that i need to do one i need to
find myself a decked out box tango
announces that there's some decked out
boxes available and they're gone in
seconds he said there was eight
and i've been looking around and i
haven't found a single one there we go
we got ourselves a box one more down
that means at the end of the episode we
can continue the tradition of playing
some more deck down now you may or may
not know but there's a bit of a
resistance going on there's mycelium
spreading around and it turns out a
bunch of people are interested so i've
got in touch with them and i've
organized for us all to have our very
first
meeting
why is cub on my barge a lot of strange
things going on
i i did i did not sanction this
i don't think so
what is this mess
wait
no
the backup box is gone
someone bought the backup box
why am i upset that's five stacks of
diamonds i'm upset because it takes so
long to make how many diamonds is that
we have almost got three stacks of
diamond blocks we're gonna be up there
as one of the richest hermits it's now
time for us
to go and have our mycelium meeting down
the chute we go how did you get an arrow
in your head
i shot myself
welcome everyone to the official
mycelium resistance what is that
you were interrupted by by some note
blocks i think uh
this is right on top of decked out right
it's a super secret location
literally one block down and you've got
decked out it's right there
i mean that brings me basically to why
i'm having this meeting you guys have
all signed up i'm getting really
interrupted by decked out
a lot of stealth going on right now
so you guys have all signed up including
xb who is he's with us
halloween hello everybody the reason i
kind of called this here is partly
because of the whole decked out thing
but this mycelium base isn't fit for
purpose well one you can hear decked out
all the time and two
it's not secret at all everyone knows
the way in this was like a recruitment
thing so
since we're all like a gang now we all
know why we're here and what we're doing
then i think what we should do is take
another location and make it our base
and never show the entrance
on camera
that way it's smart we can have yeah
yeah it's getting kind of funky down
here too i i'd prefer if we moved out to
be honest yeah i mean it's never never
going to be a permanent location but it
means that the mayor and his
particularly his enforcer can't can't
find us because they they they think
we're here they know they know
everyone's seen my videos they know
where the entrance is we're a little
close to town hall right now we are
caught leaving one day by cub fan so i'm
pretty sure
earlier so
like it's ultra compromised
it's decked out go it comes actually
just below and playing decked out
i could see them they're they're very
pious so we need to we need to find a
new location for the mycelium resistance
so that we can
resist what are we resisting exactly
yeah i was wondering that too to be
honest
you know you guys you know why we're
here we're oh well not really but of
course
we're here we're here oh yeah
killed by the beast
spoiler
so we
we are here
to send scar a message
that's my celia resistance
what what message is it exactly
yeah what is that what's that what is
the message actually
it's about the principle it is about the
principle okay it is the
the principle sending scar a message
message
are you writing that down
yes oh yeah i got that i'm taking notes
i have a very good memory i'm going to
refer to that later anyone questions why
we're doing this if
any of this ever at any point makes no
sense at all you tell them it's a matter
of principle and it's about sending scar
a message
oh right okay and we got to do this
principle
about sending score a message and that's
what it's about so is that three
exclamation marks or five i'd say five
it's definitely fine
the more they ask the more exclamation
marks
because at this point it is about the
principle it is about the principle
really if anyone's ever confused it's
about the principle yeah yes okay let's
let's go and find let's go find a place
with a new face that is nowhere near
decked out yeah okay sounds like a plan
good job xp you did a great job
now that the mycelium resistance has had
its first meeting i think we should
probably hide who the members are
just in case someone comes looking in
fact we should probably destroy all
trace of mycelium resistance nothing to
see here just a whole lot of mushrooms
get get it because it's a it's a whole
okay right so so what we need to do
before we vacate this area is i don't
want to leave this looking unfinished so
i reckon we just block off this a tunnel
is no longer needed we are vacating the
premises we are evacuating
so we just need to make this look a
whole lot more done than it currently is
so anyone that does happen to stumble up
across the old base won't suspect
a thing there we go all blocked off with
mycelium so it just looks like we're
still working on the project but i just
had another idea for a brilliant sign i
heard that mumbo jumbo is the leader of
the resistance it looks like multiple
people have come in and done signs in
fact it was all me
we're going to take all of this stuff
with us and we're going to vamp straight
out of here all that's missing really is
some cobwebs and this place looks
seriously abandoned
if they fall for that sign i mean that's
hilarious okay resistance hq is now
officially evacuated we have our we have
our team of fun guys
and now it's time to look for a new
place
for the mycelium resistance but again
that will never be shown on camera
because otherwise all the other guys
will be able to see exactly where we are
particularly scar and b dubs and cub
they'll know where the base is so you
could keep guessing where it is but i'm
gonna start excavating off camera
the place where we are going to found
the mycelium resistance
base do you see that in the background
do you see that little sign
that says resistance on it
i don't know if that was just that
that's a coincidence
in broken tea bags is this this has been
one of the weirdest episodes today
i don't even know what to say
i'll be honest with you i spent most of
this episode collecting leaves for the
hedge games and it looks like no one
submitted more so we might be in real
competition to win the thing
so now before we end the episode i want
to go and play some decked out one day
i'll get this flight exactly right
so over here i have been collecting the
nether set and i actually bought another
set uncommon for a few coins from
impulse and
i just need one more i've got
a bunch of other things so we're going
to do a couple of runs we're going to
see what we can get hopefully you'll go
a bit better this time key in door open
compass we know the drill by now all
right deck box in
the run
begins that sounds like there's a
ravager just on the other side of this
door
oh come on
[Music]
let's go for it straight away straight
off straight off the bat
i hate this thing so much
[Music]
okay
no
why is there a ravager just there
wait
nothing in here
[Music]
no is this it
okay we got the loot box token
but there is a ravager
literally round this corner
okay let's play this really safe i want
to do a bit more exploring do not swim
down ravager swimming pool below
we're not gonna get past ravages very
easily in these tunnels
let's see if we can find ourselves some
soul flames here lies you
think that might be true
nothing in the web of lies
nothing in these barrels
[Music]
i'm getting a bit stressed now
i've gone deep into the dungeon
and i'm not finding any exposed blue
flames or any loot whatsoever
okay nothing in here
i'm getting a lot of clank going around
here
[Music]
okay we got this
there's a key up there
is that is that meant to be gotten or is
that just a teasing
i have a feeling i have a feeling
there's ravages here in fact i'm so
close to the entrance now i've done a
full cycle
and i didn't find anything
where's the exit
[Music]
there's a ravager there's a ravager
there
[Music]
coins
where's the exit
[Music]
i think we leave we leave
we leave
come on
we did it what do we get loot finder
loot finder
or beast sense we'll go for loot finder
we got out of there with a win
now we submit our loot box token
maui i'm recording okay well we got
dragon set common wither set unique
and wither set uncommon and two decked
out coins
that is massive
that is absolutely massive because
that's well that's a unique is
so good i don't think i have any withers
stuff at the moment but that's two of
the same set and the unique is the best
one
and then i actually have already the
dragon set rare
so unfortunately it didn't give me the
nether that i needed but it's uh it's
helping us along the way
and then we've got to return the shulker
there
to tango so we can keep
so his supplies don't run dry and i also
noticed ancient debris donation box for
lodestones you know what we are going
because this game has been so good we
are going to do something
very very nice while the game is
resetting we're gonna travel back
to the base
and we are going to donate every single
bit of ancient debris from the
netherright throne to tango's game it's
not not really another right throne
anymore is it just a netherright
log
so 11 ancient debris
being donated i've renamed it from green
so he knows it's from me
oh no
oh no oh stupid me
i said earlier when am i gonna get that
flight right
there we go
11 ancient debris
and now we wait for this to reset there
we go
let's do another run
another compass
i can hear that ravager on the other
side of the wall let's go
oh no oh no i didn't go in
i'm sure tango won't mind
there is a ravager
oh he can't i don't think he can get to
me
from there
okay looks like
looks like it's
this direction my loot
i love this game
it's both spooky and fun for exploring
oh please tell me this loot isn't in the
forest i hate the forest it's number one
cause of death is the forest
hopefully i can find a secret now i
tried to get down there last time
there's a barrel now i think you need a
couple of ender pearls to get down there
although you see this like
dark outline around corrales i wonder if
there's something there that allows you
to bounce
but i don't want to risk it
i really don't dungeon keys are very
valuable at the moment
there's something on that sign too
i can't quite make out what it says no
it's not worth it
okay there is definitely a ravager
[Music]
in there there always is a ravager in
there
i didn't see that before
i feel like there's got to be a secret
in this room
i really
do there's secrets everywhere but i'm
not very good at finding them
[Music]
oh
secret
okay i need to throw something on there
i'll throw my compass for now
yes and we'll get some decked out coins
sweet i think there would be a soul
flame there i'm very unlucky on the soul
flames i never seem to find any
right and we got our compass back right
let's be sensible here because there is
is there anything behind the waterfall
more secrets no rewards
and no soul flame either
there's something underwater as well
bubble columns
there's got to be some ravages around
here somewhere
oh there's one there there's one there
no
why did i think that the cobweb was a
good idea
oh my god a proper headbutt dang it well
not every run is successful and i forgot
to sleep in the bed ah
you turn your back for one second and
the ravages get you but i nailed that
flight that time so there's a few things
that i need to do next episode and you
may notice that today is episode 43
and my next episode is 44.
now 44 is the famous episode
because in my base there's a bunch
of chickens and i think episode 44
is the episode that i do a lot of them
kill this chicken with an anvil invent
nicknames for all the hermits
in particular
there is one chicken that says have a
breakdown in episode 44.
great
so we all look forward to that and i'm
afraid that is the end of today's
episode i'm gonna spend the remainder of
the off-camera time filling up these
shulker boxes because these shulker
boxes are going to be my next round
of barge mystery boxes but it's not
going to be the same as last time
they're not just buy a box this time
it's
find a box so we're gonna send people on
treasure hunts that they pay for it
should be a lot of fun but for now i
shall see you in the next episode good
bye